

### **GUIDO VAN DIJK**

**FRONT-END DEVELOPER** 

#### WHO AM I?

My name is Guido van Dijk, 23 years old, and born in The Netherlands.

I am a Front-end developer with 5 years of design and web development experience.
I specialize in Vue.js and JavaScript ES-Next, which I use to create optimized, accessible websites and applications, in a short amount of time.

My main objective is to grow as a developer, working with all kinds of techniques to expand my knowledge about developing websites and applications as both front- and backend.

#### **SKILL SET**

JavaScript, Vue.js, C#, Java, Kotlin, PHP, MySQL, NoSQL, (S)CSS, HTML, Scrum, Git, Agile, Bitbucket, Atlassian, Jira, Photoshop, Sketch, Adobe XD,

### **INFORMATION**

- van.quido@hotmail.com
- GitHub
- LinkedIn
- +31 6 57662230

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER • THE VALLEY • JULY 2018 – JULY 2022

I developed campaign websites for Postcode-, Vrienden-, and BuurtLoterij. I helped expand the front-end of our sales platform Nominow with Vue.js. And developed client websites for Nike, Tommy Hilfiger, and their daughter companies with frameworks that work best for their use-cases, products, and specifications.

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER / UI DESIGNER • FBI DESIGN • SEP 2017 – JUNE 2018

I designed and developed WordPress websites for a wide array of clients, large and small located in and around Haarlem.

## FREELANCE UX/UI DESIGNER • NEXTAIL • DEC 2016 – JAN 2017

I was responsible for setting up the campaigns and creating content for the social media accounts of the Blokker holding (Bart Smit, Leenbakker, Intertoys, and Cook&Co). I designed promotional products for the 70<sup>th</sup> birthday of De Huishouds Beurs and created a design for the new website of Intertoys.

#### **EDUCATION**

DEGREE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY • CURRENT • HOGESCHOOL INHOLLAND HAARLEM

DEGREE DESIGN FOR INTERACTION • 2019 • MEDIA COLLEGE AMSTERDAM